Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Grades and enrollment data, 1957-2007; Accession 2016-A-050
  - Yale College 2008 Spring Grades
    - American Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Anthropology, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Applied Math, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Applied Physics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Arabic, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Architecture, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Art, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Astronomy, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Chemical Engineering, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Chemistry, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Chinese, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Classics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - College Seminars, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Computer Science, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Comparative Literature, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Calhoun College Seminar, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Morse College Seminar, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Directed Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Drama, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - East Asian Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Economics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Electrical Engineering, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Epidemiology of Microbial Disease, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - English, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Ethics, Politics, Economics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Environmental Engineering, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Environmental Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Film Media Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - French, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - German, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - German Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Hindi, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - History, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - History of Art, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - History of Science Medicine, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Humanities, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Italian, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Korean, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Latin, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Latin American Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Linguistics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Law, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Literature, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Management, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Mathematics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Music, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Philosophy, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Physics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Politicial Science, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Portuguese, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Psychology, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Religious Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Russian, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Sociology, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Spanish, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Statistics, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Theater Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Women's Gender Sexuality Studies, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Peking University, 2008 Spring (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Yale College Distinctions
    - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 2007 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 2010 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 2011 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 2012 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 2013 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Yale College Phi Beta Kappa
    - PBK Spring 2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Commencement 2006 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - PBK Fall 2006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Phi Beta Kappa 2005 Fall (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - PBK Spring 2005 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - PBK 2004 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Phi Beta Kappa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - PBK Fall 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Fall 2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - PBK Spring 2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - PBK Fall 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Spring 2001 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - PBK Spring 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - PBK Spring 1999 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - PBK 2007 Fall (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - PBK 2014 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - PBK Fall 2013 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - PBK May 2013 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - PBK Fall 2012 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Phi Beta Kappa 2012 Spring (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - PBK 2011 Fall (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - PBK 2011 Spring Commencement (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - PBK 2010 Fall (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - PBK 2010 Spring (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - PBk 2009 Spring (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - PBK 2008 Fall (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - PBK May 2008 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - PBK Spring 2007 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Yale College General Honors
    - 1999 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - 2012 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - 2011 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - 2010 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - 2009 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - 2008 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - 2007 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - 2006 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 2005 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - 2003 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 2001 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - 2000 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Yale College Prizes
    - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - 2003 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - 2002 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - 2001 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - 2000 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - 1970-1990 (Box 6, Folder 60-61)
  - Yale College: Yale-in-London, Yale-in Beijing, Norfolk, Enrollment Counts
    - Yale in Beijing 2012 Spring (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Yale in Beijing 2011 Fall (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Yale in Beijing 2011 Spring (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Yale in Beijing 2011 Spring (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 2010 Fall Yale in Beijing (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 2010 Spring Yale in Beijing (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 2009 Fall Yale in Beijing (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Yale in Beijing 2009 Spring (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Yale-in-Beijing 06/07, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Peking Univ 2008 Fall (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Peking Univ 2007 Fall (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Peking Univ Spring 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Peking 2008 Spring (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Yale-China Teaching Fellowship, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Yale in London Summer 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Visiting London Fall 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Yale in London Summer 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Spring 1996 Visiting London (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Visiting Yale Spring 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - British Studies Summer 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Yale in London Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Yale in London Spring 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Yale in London Fall 2001 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - British Studies Summer 1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Yale In London Summer 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 2011 Spring Yale in London (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Yale in London Spring 2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Summer 2003 British Studies Courses (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Yale in London Spring 2003 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Yale-in London Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Yale in London Summer 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Yale-in London 2007 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Yale in London Summer 2005 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Summer 2004 British Studies Courses (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Yale in London Spring 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - British Studies Yale in London Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Yale in London Spring 2004 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Yale in London Summer 2006 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - British Studies Summer 2006 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Yale in London 2009 Spring (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Yale in London Summer 2013 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Yale in London Summer 2012 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Yale in London Summer 2009 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Yale in London Summer 2008 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Yale in London 2008 Spring (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Yale in London Summer 2007 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Yale in London Spring 2013 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Yale in London Summer 2011 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - 2012 Spring Yale in London (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Yale in London Summer 2010 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Yale in London 2010 Spring (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Norfolk Summer 1996 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Norfolk Summer 1997 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Norfolk Summer 1998 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Norfolk Summer 1999 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Norfolk Summer 2000 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Norfolk Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Norfolk Summer 2002 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Norfolk Summer 2003 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Norfolk Summer Art 2004 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Norfolk Summer 2006 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Norfolk Summer 2007 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Norfolk Summer 2008 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Yale College: Enrollment Counts
    - 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 64-65)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 66-67)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 68-69)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 70-71)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 72-73)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)